Music
Waiting
Clicquot
Certainly.
Yes.
Good morning
Good morning.
Today.
That's what it looked like.
Today
With the members of this group.
Who's the photographer?
I'm not a photographer.
Yes, I am.
What's the vlog today?
Sky Tree
Sky Tree Vlog
What's that?
So... let's go.
Let's go, I'm hungry.
He said, “Hey, I want to go eat a hamburger now.
And what's more...
It's not a hamburger, it's meat.
Four hamburgers.
Meat.
Vegetable meat.
I heard they're going out to eat.
I was wondering if I could go with you.
I'd like to ask her if I can go with her.
I'd like to ask her.
Koremitsu says he wants to go.
He brought his camera today.
That's right.
Let's go.
Cheers.
Recently.
Nion gratin soup. Nion Gratin Soup
What?
Nion gratin soup?
Why do you feel like you're doomed?
Nion gratin soup.
Let's go eat cheese.
Let's go eat.
What kind of food is that?
It's just onion soup.
With cheese on top.
And a baguette on top.
And it's soaked.
And there's cheese in it.
Cheese on top.
It's so delicious!
Nion gratin soup!
Neon gratin soup? Yes.
Cheese.
I got it!
Looks too good!
I'm starving.
This one?
This is avocado cheese.
And this is?
The burger of the day.
Avocado mozzarella cheeseburger.
This is wild out.
Looks good.
That's pretty cool.
Smidaga's got a cheese dog kind of thing and...
Stone onions.
Thanks, guys.
Various.
Many, many, many.
various various
Various.
Thank you for dinner.
It doesn't look good, does it?
That's why I had to take it now.
I couldn't take too many comments.
You're right.
It's all subtitled.
It's a great blue Famima.
What?
It's black!
Wait a minute.
What did you say?
That's a blue Famima!
It's black!
No, it's not.
That's scary.
What are you looking at?
You're looking in the wrong place.
What do you mean?
The fortunes here...
There are so many today.
Why are you being so negative?
It's not a bad day.
Why?
Because it's today.
It's not that bad.
I mean, there's always a way up.
Come on.
Today.
Kitch.
That's Kitch!
That's today.
Is that how it's gonna be?
I can see it in the back. You'll find out in the back.
There are two of them today.
Call them.
App.
Same.
Sick.
Lost
Townspeople
Will not show up
New construction
Let's not see each other
Traveling
Socializing
It's bad for everything.
Do all things
Careful
I wish
If you request it long enough, it will be cured.
Lost
It will be hard
Townspeople will show up late
Moving will be bad
Marriages will be bad
It's all right.
You will get what you want in life
You will get well
Lost
Lost things
Will come out
Townspeople will come
You will move into a new house
Marriages will be good, all marriages will be good.
Traveling will be good.
Next.
Your wish will come true
Then you'll be happy and you'll be happy.
Let's be happy
Let's be happy and modified Let us be happy and corrected
Sickness will be slowed down and cured
Lost things
Will be found late
Townspeople will appear
We will endure many hardships along the way
All will be well with the new building, moving, and relationships
New house, new home, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house, new house
It's great
I'll go play with these then... bye-bye bye...
I hear you're taking these home... and I want to go home... but I heard that even at the same base... you're going home differently depending on your number.
I've never been here before today...
When I was a kid I only ever got “big luck” and I thought it was the only way to get it
Why did I finally get the wrong one?
There's always been a base.
I thought it was only Daikichi.
Well, it's the same, but different...
All right, I've never been out of the house today. Me neither...
Let's go sightseeing in Asakusa.
Let's go.
What happened?
I just tied the knot.
This way, this way, this way.
I just tied it.
Haruma, it's ripped to shreds.
He ripped it and dropped it.
And the hook just snapped.
I'm done.
If I can get this tied right, maybe it'll be better.
So...
Tenpashira
Oh, I've been punished.
We're getting punished physically.
Well, then, you'll have to get mad at us.
Why?
Sure, sure.
But if we buy him a drink now, he might not like it.
Why not? What's up with that?
You're doing a great job.
You're right. You're right.
We're on base. We're on base. Maybe if I buy you a drink, it'll do you some good.
Yeah, yeah, it might do you some good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, let's go.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
Here you go.
Thank you. Thank you.
Wow.
That's good.
Looks so good!
Wow, I can eat it.
Bon appétit.
It's so good!
You're swallowing!
Everyone's swallowing.
Wow, it looks delicious!
It's so good.
What does it taste like?
The batter is so thick.
It tastes more like vegetable than meat.
It tastes like vegetables.
Onions, you know, sweet.
Yeah.
They're pretty big.
With gravy.
It really is.
Ta-da!
I'm going in now.
I really don't want it.
It's floating a little bit.
It's a mess!
It's only allowed in Asakusa. I'm only allowed in Asakusa anymore.
I really think so.
Let's enter!
Enter!
Attraction!
It's like a kafelni ride!
I'm starting to float.
Wow!
This is nice.
Are you excited?
I'm floating.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're about halfway through.
So...
That's it.
What? Where are we?
It's getting late.
Maybe it's just as well.
Where?
You want to see?
See?
Hey.
We're almost there.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
Already.
445?
It says 350 here.
This is 350 meters.
Oh, my God.
350 meters to the death.
This way, sir.
What are you all doing now?
This is amazing!
It's crazy!
It's not here.
It's in the way! Don't get in my way.
Don't tell me to get out of the way.
It's just a little bit of electricity.
But, you know, we're so far away from the school.
Can you read “school zone”?
Can you?
Look, there's something green on the road. I see a stop sign.
Yes, a school zone. I've got bad eyesight.
School zone.
There's something like Tokyo Dome.
Wow, the quality is much better. It's beautiful. It's so beautiful.
The sky!
It's the Tokyo Dome!
It's a little bit glashglash, but it's good to take a picture.
Is it leaking a lot?
It's leaking.
It's leaking so much.
It's so beautiful.
I think I'm going to go to the glass floor now.
Bye-bye.
Gross!
Wow, that's amazing.
Since we're here, I'd like to take pictures with everyone.
I'd like to do that.
Mr. Lunopin.
I'm scared.
I can't look down.
Seriously, it's pretty bad when you look down, isn't it?
I was looking through the camera, too, you know.
Once you're cool, it's over.
Yeah, pretty much over.
We had a great day.
What did you do today?
Today...
I bought tickets to the Skytree...
Fine.
I went out to eat.
I came back. I'm back.
I went to the Sky Tree.
And here we are now.
Surprisingly, you can enjoy it to the fullest.
I did a lot of walking.
Half a day
I'll take a look at the maintenance system later.
Okay, here's the announcement.
I'll put the message below.
June 8th.
at the hall in Yokohama
We will be holding a one-man event
The title of the event is “Love Ann School”.
It will be a day where you can see us in a new way.
We are going to have a day where you can see
And I think it will be a day where we can make memories
I think it will be a day where we can make memories that we have never made before.
We hope to see you all there!
Please come and join us.
Bye-bye!
Good Button
Subscribe to our channel
Thank you!
Bye-bye!